that this is a very
good afternoon friends bf with
another set of questions you are welcome to and
request should arrive safely to the mission
possible you are lieutenant or else kasana and
exam me here and there set up questions will take the
third question of the day in the this ftu and
time to participate in the same question
and he is the question and this cream editing
directly screen squashed you are driving
item and it people will take you will get you all
the process what will we do is follow him
overtake him in this study
go after them and do the thing and
fight with them and
quaker guava now fight or
mentally note down the number and report to the
authorities you will mentally set that number in your mind
and report to the authorities
that they have done this to you
this heart to your display job or phone ring
why won't you tell that they didn't like this thing so
now on family connect 10
and join us on this an old campaign is this
quiz contest end  Now you can win
exciting prizes, you can get this
knowledge for the road safety. These are all questions related to the
things that happen to us on a daily basis.
You
can participate by participating because
on a daily basis we
use things in some way or the other, so somewhere
these are connected to us and the things that
happen on a daily basis, the same questions are being
asked to you. All these questions are related to our interest,
okay, and our aim of
doing all these things is that how can
we make our day more just, how can we make
maximum people aware,
regarding this road safety, as you
know, this is our nine three today and we
welcome you to our squashed
Dana Nuvvu, we want you to
also be a part of this campaign.
Join in the office with your family and friends. You can
join it with your friends so that
you can also make them a part of this campaign to
make your day more just.  I can take
a small step forward in making their life better. I do
n't know how many
accidents happen every day due to a small
carelessness. Assam
says that you people should not be careless, keep
yourself focused, even a small
mistake can take someone's life, can
lose someone's loved ones, can snatch away someone's loved ones
and so we would request you
that whenever you are
driving every day, please
follow all the rules. Fulfill
your responsibilities and
contribute in making our roads safe and take
this entire campaign forward by joining us so that
we can join as many people as possible with us and take this
one thing that we want to bring, we
want to make our roads safe and just, we can take it further
and this caravan should keep joining
with all of you because only with the cooperation of all of you
we will be able to make our mission possible, we will be
able to switch off our bra mode, only then this
entire combing of ours will be possible.  This is a show
called Drive C for Mission
Possible yes we can make the best possible with
your support we cannot do it alone but
with your support we can help
to change the condition of roads and major roads
ourselves we can see all over my screen the
question is well you can be a part of this
and win more exciting prizes we
play 5 to 6 questions for every day in grand congress
with you with new questions you
can participate in those questions your first two
days you can also ask your family and friends to
participate in it
and your knowledge which is your
interest again related to road knowledge you can
enhance it our main motive is that
how can we help you as much as possible
regarding road safety these
small things of roads and the
raw which we deliver on this and the
guava behaviour which we get every day  How
can we change this, this is our only aim and this is what we
want that whoever you connect with us,
those people can also be safe,
join us and
help us in making your roach safe, so the question on the developed me screen,
what is above, so I will
read it for you, you are driving
item and tricks on vinegar white color over
take and swing swing get you into
prostitution follow medicine tomorrow ad one
thing and five words not the number one
report to the authority to display this,
this is a very simple question, you
face this thing on daily basis, when you are going, there are many
people who
over take you, this means they do the
job in the wrong way, so
you have to decide what will be your answer,
Jyoti added, give a sure answer so that
you have a chance to hide the gift, the
important part of this is the
five questions that we bring, you
can participate in all those five questions and
win exciting prizes  This is our
full right, next it is up
to 300 frames, so you can come on it daily,
join us and
also participate in it, its
results are our issue which comes at
10:00 in the night, piece by piece and in that
our results are announced on
daily basis,
our results are
shown in it, we request you
that by joining you you will see
how many prizes you have won, very very
interesting, this is somewhere a small
step to make your day safe,
for the safety of yourself and your loved ones, so we want you to
be a part of this entire campaign with me and help us to
make your day just
because only when we change, the country will change,
if we all
fulfill our responsibilities every day, whether we
mean we are in the district or we are
bikers or we are in Bigg Boss or we are
driving a car, if we all
fulfill our responsibilities, whatever
route road you have, our  There are rules and regulations, if
we follow them today then somewhere or the other
you will be able to make your day safe, so
our request to you is that take
care of yourself and your loved ones when you
drive, please if you are
travelling for a short distance, right now we
request you finally that the
helmet creates a covering, it
creates a layer over your head
which can protect you from any injury or
accident, it
is very important and whenever you buy a helmet, we
request you to always buy a helmet with ISI mark
and its fastener is
its belt, definitely wear it and
always buy a helmet of the right size,
nashad information type because if it is a
thick helmet then it will not stay on your head,
viral e love in accident and red
chilli and now it will come out due to which whatever
protection your health should get
during that time, you will not get it
and if you wear it too tight then
somewhere or the other it will make you feel cold
and  Anyway, juvenile driving it's very
important to make
drivers to be accountable for girls,
first of all driving pinpointed and if you
want to take your children along, if you are going to drop your children to school
then mix and you make them
wear helmets as well, helmets are actually
very important for those children also
whom you are going to drop them, so when they go to school then
take a helmet of their size, they do
not wear helmets just for show or there are no
rules and regulations to show others
and that you are
wearing helmet to show off to the police, here you are
wearing it on the seat, here you are
wearing it because of the cameras, you are
wearing it because of the challan, we do not have to do that thing,
we have to do those things for our own safety, for the
safety of our loved ones, so till
we think that
we are doing this for ourselves, we are doing it for our own safety, then
somewhere or the other we
can bring more changes, if we are doing it
for the police or because there are cameras
We are here because of the challan, that is why
our slogan is not for the challan, not for
false pride, war room CST is
for the lives of our loved ones, so we are
explaining to you that this is not for others,
it is for us too, it is for our Shetty, in the
morning I request
you that please use this only mission and American,
you drink juice, answer to
your rules and regulations, now follow them, so
one tax is very important, now Dixit
Yummy, you will have questions on the screen,
register your answers as quickly as possible, bring
your friends and family members with you,
you should involve Jio,
this sequence is
related to road safety, in this you have to enhance your knowledge,
so I am giving you this once again,
you are driving items and tricks
Pennyroyal overtax, you will get you in the
process, you will always be physically and over
ticket thing in the fight with Ashwatik Yasmin,
third number one reported to them  Authorities
here home to show your display what you
saw this how much resolution is the question you answer modern
whose and Ravi you have a chance to
win the price you are a minority
see its answer now only chance to
win the question you participate offer after 2 hours
again a new setup question will come m
viewers welcome to come back and
join us and drive this forward
see all these trends
she will request you to follow this
because it is very important a
jhal loot lo loot loot
loot
one by one turn on
hey you can see the question and on the screen
you are driving item and rate speed vinegar
white color over the issue was wearing a
tune in to prostitute 151 overtake chin in
more mentally no name and report to the
authorities to show your display please
answer this and you are with us and this picture of
ours will last till then you
can subscribe to it subscribe the
question changes in 2 hours  If yes, then you
can participate in those five
and become a part of our campaign.
So come and join us and let's make a new
beginning. To save yourself and your
loved ones, to
celebrate your day,
you too can become a part of that campaign and
with us in this change that we
want to bring, we want to make our protest just,
you can help us in making our protest just by participating with us and
joining us.
So Dashrath
Question of the Day, right now you can
participate in the questions left above and you can participate in that effort.
Thank you so much for the Dev evolves into
Varna Kasana show, a righteous living and always be with us.
Our Abir and other team members
are Fikars, they will come with you and
they will do the new question. You have 2 hours to
participate here, they can participate there.
9 News Questions. Thank you so much for the
specific Henry t****